

Student Data Science and Artificial Intelligence. Interests in mathematics and problem-solving naturally led me to this field after a detour in the economics, law and tax field. Staying at the forefront of cutting-edge technologies and collaborating with like-minded peers at the university has been an enriching experience so far. I believe AI has the greatest potential to change the world we live in and I want to contribute to this development.

Camiel Schmeitz

Phone:

+31 637557073

E-Mail:

Camielschmeitz@gmail.com

Linkedin:

linkedin.com/in/camielschmeitz/

Skill Highlights

- Project management
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solver
- Innovative
- Both independent and teamfocused
- Java, Python, Git, SQL, PyTorch

Languages

Dutch – C2 English – C1 German – A2

Hobby's

In my free time I like to play football or you can often find me in the gym. In addition, I like to read.

Experience

02/2018 - 02/2022

L.M. Meijers Bv

- L.M. Meijers Bv specializes in top-quality paramedical aids and training materials.
- Warehouse employee

10/2020 - 06/2023

Zuyderland

- Multi-site hospital, care centers, mental health care, rehabilitation, home care, youth/elderly health care, domestic help.
- Employee in (demented) elderly healthcare institutions such as Aldenhof, Lemborgh, De Kollenberg and Hof van Serviam

09/2023 - Present

Freelance

- Independent contractor for Remotask, focusing on the assessment of large language models (LLMs), mainly for Google Gemini.
- Previously engaged as a door-to-door sales representative for Spark, promoting sustainable products including solar panels, insulation, and heating and cooling solutions.

Education

2013-2020

Trevianum Scholengroep

Atheneum

2020 - present

Maastricht University

- BSc Fiscal Economics (2020-2022, not graduated)
- BSc Data Science and Artificial Intelligence (2022-present)

References

References available on request